universe = [
    {
        question: "What is the full form of MOM ?",
        options: ['Moon Orbiter Mission ', 'Mars Orbiter Mission' , 'Mangalayan Orbital Mission', 'Mutliverse of Madness'],
        answer: 'Mars Orbiter Mission'
    }
]

sports = [
    {
        question: "The famous football player Maradona belongs to which among the following countries?",
        options: ['Brazil','Chile','Argentina','Italy'],
        answer: 'Argentina'
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following Indian Sports Team is also known as “The Bhangra Boys?",
        options: ['Cricket Team','Hockey Team','Kabaddi Team','Football Team'],
        answer: 'Football Team'
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has won the maximum number of medals in the all time history of Commonwealth Games?",
        options: ['Australia','England','India','Canada'],
        answer: 'Australia'
    },
    {
        question: "What does the globe in the ICC World Cup Trophy symbolise?",
        options: ['World','All participating nations','Cricket Ball','Unity'],
        answer: 'Cricket Ball'
    },
    {
        question: "Which organization awards the 'Pierre de Coubertin Medal'?",
        options: ['The United Nations','The International Monetary Fund','The International Olympic Committee','The International Atomic Energy Agency'],
        answer: 'The International Olympic Committee'
    },
    {
        question: "Among the following athletes who won a gold medal for India in Olympics?",
        options: ['PV Sindhu','Milkha Singh','Abhinav Bindra','Bajarang Punia'],
        answer: 'Abhinav Bindra'
    }
]

sciTech = [
    {
        question: "Which country recently launched a driver-less bullet train with the speed up to 350 km/h?",
        options: ['Japan','China','Singapore','USA'],
        answer: 'China'
    },
    {
        question: "Global code hosting platform GitHub, which recently launched its operations in India, is owned by which technological company?",
        options: ['Google','Microsoft','Amazon','Apple'],
        answer: 'Microsoft'
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has won the maximum number of medals in the all time history of Commonwealth Games?",
        options: ['Australia','England','India','Canada'],
        answer: 'Australia'
    },
    {
        question: "What does the globe in the ICC World Cup Trophy symbolise?",
        options: ['World','All participating nations','Cricket Ball','Unity'],
        answer: 'Cricket Ball'
    },
    {
        question: "Which organization awards the 'Pierre de Coubertin Medal'?",
        options: ['The United Nations','The International Monetary Fund','The International Olympic Committee','The International Atomic Energy Agency'],
        answer: 'The International Olympic Committee'
    },
    {
        question: "Among the following athletes who won a gold medal for India in Olympics?",
        options: ['PV Sindhu','Milkha Singh','Abhinav Bindra','Bajarang Punia'],
        answer: 'Abhinav Bindra'
    }
]

artCulture = [
    {
        question: "The birth anniversary of which social reformer was celebrated on January 3?",
        options: ['Narayana Guru','Vinoba Bhave','Pandita Ramabhai','Savitribai Phule'],
        answer: 'Savitribai Phule'
    },
    {
        question: "Which Indian monument has found place in the Shanghai Cooperation Organisation's '8 Wonders of SCO' list?",
        options: ['Taj Mahal','Statue of Unity','Konark Sun Temple','Ajanta Caves'],
        answer: 'Statue of Unity'
    },
    {
        question: "When is the national Tourism day celebrated across the country?",
        options: ['January 23','January 24','January 25','January 26'],
        answer: 'January 25'
    },
    {
        question: "What does the globe in the ICC World Cup Trophy symbolise?",
        options: ['World','All participating nations','Cricket Ball','Unity'],
        answer: 'Cricket Ball'
    },
    {
        question: "Which country recently set a Guinness World Record for the highest altitude fashion show event ever held?",
        options: ['China','Nepal','India','Brazil'],
        answer: 'Nepal'
    },
    {
        question: "Which film recently won the Oscar for best picture, which is also the first non- English film to win the award?",
        options: ['Les Misérables','Irishman','Parasite','Border'],
        answer: 'Parasite'
    }
]
